<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Context Podcast</title>
    <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Context Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 23:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://thecontext.github.com/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 26: How It’s Made — Juno</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/26-how-its-made-juno/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/26-how-its-made-juno/</guid>
      <description>We continue our How It’s Made series: Hannes and Artur are talking about how Juno, the company Artur works in, does product engineering.
Links:
 Multi-tiered technical support Git branching model Rolling release Kotlin SAM (single abstract method) issue Domic — UI abstraction, similar to internal Juno one Multi-tier architecture Gradle Kotlin DSL Mainframer Bitrise Elasticsearch Grafana Juno Careers Artur’s slides about Juno Kotlin experiences Artur’s blog with details about IoC, Reactive approaches and more  Hosts  Artur Dryomov: Twitter, GitHub, blog Hannes Dorfmann: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 25: How It’s Made — Freeletics</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/25-how-its-made-freeletics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/25-how-its-made-freeletics/</guid>
      <description>This episode is starting a series about Android application development. Hannes and Artur are talking about how Freeletics, the company Hannes works in, does product engineering.
Links:
 Freeletics Video: Working at Freeletics John Locke Koin RxRedux CoRedux Mosby The Test Pyramid Freeletics Engineering Blog  Hosts  Artur Dryomov: Twitter, GitHub, blog Hannes Dorfmann: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 24: Ok Multiplatform with Jesse Wilson and Egor Andreevich</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/24-multiplatform/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/24-multiplatform/</guid>
      <description>In this episode Artem and Hannes chatted with Jesse and Egor from Square about multiplatform development with Kotlin.
Jesse and Egor shared their experience of migrating Okio to Kotlin and which strategies they have applied to make it multiplatform ready.
Announcement: Please participate in this survey to give us feedback how we can make this podcast better.
Links:
 Okio on GitHub Announcing Okio 2: Our fast + simple I/O library, Okio, has a new release that supports Kotlin JApicmp: binary compatibility reporting The Context Podcast Survey: Help us make the show better  Guests  Egor Andreevich: Twitter, GitHub, blog Jesse Wilson: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Hosts  Artem Zinnatullin: Twitter, GitHub, blog Hannes Dorfmann: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 23: Rise of the Machines (droidcon Berlin 2018)</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/23-droidcon-machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/23-droidcon-machines/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve collaborated with droidcon Berlin 2018 (June 25) where Hannes was speaking about MVI, and they&amp;rsquo;ve recorded panel discussions for us and allowed us to publish them with our commentary.
Thanks droidcon Berlin and the local Berlin Android community for collaborating with us.
Guests  Dr. Roman Belter Hoi Lam: Twitter Jürgen Fey: Twitter Meghan Kane: Twitter Silvia Cambie: Twitter  Hosts  Kevin McDonagh: Twitter  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 23: Rise of the Machines (droidcon Berlin 2018)</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/23-machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/23-machines/</guid>
      <description>Thanks droidcon Berlin and the local Berlin Android community for collaborating with us.
Guests  Dr. Roman Belter Hoi Lam: Twitter Jürgen Fey: Twitter Meghan Kane: Twitter Silvia Cambie: Twitter  Hosts  Kevin McDonagh: Twitter  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 22: Women in Tech (droidcon Berlin 2018)</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/22-droidcon-women/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/22-droidcon-women/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve collaborated with droidcon Berlin 2018 (June 25) where Hannes was speaking about MVI, and they&amp;rsquo;ve recorded panel discussions for us and allowed us to publish them with our commentary.
Thanks droidcon Berlin and the local Berlin Android community for collaborating with us.
Guests  Anita Singh: Twitter Annyce Davis: Twitter Kevin McDonagh: Twitter Lara Martín: Twitter Vivien Dollinger: LinkedIn  Hosts  Daniela Gausmann: LinkedIn  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 21: Rx Must Die (droidcon Berlin 2018)</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/21-droidcon-rx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/21-droidcon-rx/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve collaborated with droidcon Berlin 2018 (June 25) where Hannes was speaking about MVI, and they&amp;rsquo;ve recorded panel discussions for us and allowed us to publish them with our commentary.
This particular episode is a panel discussion with a very controversial title Rx Must Die. As you might know, all hosts of The Context podcast have very warm feelings about Rx and it was not an easy job for us to comment, Hannes and Artur were strong enough but Artem had to bail out (oof).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 20, Part 2: public final Agile</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/20.2-agile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/20.2-agile/</guid>
      <description>Artem and Hannes continue the discussion with Alexey Alexeev about Agile, Scrum, Kanban and everything related to project management.
Links:
 Turn the Ship Around! Toyota Production System Jeff Sutherland David Anderson Kaizen  Guests  Alexey Alexeev: LinkedIn  Hosts  Artem Zinnatullin: Twitter, GitHub, blog Hannes Dorfmann: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 20, Part 1: public final Agile</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/20.1-agile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/20.1-agile/</guid>
      <description>In this episode Artem and Hannes chatted with Alexey Alexeev about Agile, Scrum, Kanban and everything related to project management.
Links:
 Turn the Ship Around! Toyota Production System Jeff Sutherland David Anderson Kaizen  Guests  Alexey Alexeev: LinkedIn  Hosts  Artem Zinnatullin: Twitter, GitHub, blog Hannes Dorfmann: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 19, Part 2: Model-View-Intent with Benoît Quenaudon from Square</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/19.2-mvi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/19.2-mvi/</guid>
      <description>We discussed the difference between MVP, MVVM and MVI, how to implement MVI, reusable components and how to test MVI based applications.
Links:
 Cycle.js Android Blueprint: ToDo App using MVI by Benoît droidcon NYC 2017 - Model-View-Intent for Android In-App Navigation with Coordinators droidcon SF 2017 - The Reactive Workflow Pattern Update Benoît&amp;rsquo;s Tweet: &amp;ldquo;We see more and more &amp;ldquo;reactive&amp;rdquo; architectures on Android but I think you&amp;rsquo;re doing it wrong if you have a subscribe in your presenter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 19, Part 1: Model-View-Intent with Benoît Quenaudon from Square</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/19.1-mvi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/19.1-mvi/</guid>
      <description>We discussed the difference between MVP, MVVM and MVI, how to implement MVI, reusable components and how to test MVI based applications.
Links:
 Cycle.js Android Blueprint: ToDo App using MVI by Benoît droidcon NYC 2017 - Model-View-Intent for Android In-App Navigation with Coordinators droidcon SF 2017 - The Reactive Workflow Pattern Update Benoît&amp;rsquo;s Tweet: &amp;ldquo;We see more and more &amp;ldquo;reactive&amp;rdquo; architectures on Android but I think you&amp;rsquo;re doing it wrong if you have a subscribe in your presenter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 18, Part 2: Android Everywhere</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/18.2-everywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/18.2-everywhere/</guid>
      <description>In the second part of episode #18 Artur, Hannes and Artem discuss Android TV, Chromecast and Android Auto.
Links:
 The Context Episode 5: Android TV with Joe Birch Android TV &amp;amp; Chill: A concept for what it would be like ordering fast-food on Android TV by Joe Birch. OpenAuto: Turns a Raspberry Pi into an Android Auto device. Artem&amp;rsquo;s car system running Android  Hosts  Artem Zinnatullin: Twitter, GitHub, blog Artur Dryomov: Twitter, GitHub, blog Hannes Dorfmann: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 18, Part 1: Android Everywhere</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/18.1-everywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/18.1-everywhere/</guid>
      <description>In the first part of episode #18 Artur, Hannes und Artem discuss Android tablets, Chromebooks and Android Wear (Wear OS).
Links:
 Fireside Chat with Matias Duarte, VP of Design, Android: Interesting interview with Matias Duarte about form factors like mobile, wearables, TV, Chromebooks and watch.  Hosts  Artem Zinnatullin: Twitter, GitHub, blog Artur Dryomov: Twitter, GitHub, blog Hannes Dorfmann: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 17: Switching Gears to C# and .NET</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/17-dot-net/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/17-dot-net/</guid>
      <description>Artur chatted with Dmitry Savchenko about C#, .NET and everything in between.
The reason is simple — we are changing our jobs as Android developers to be real enterprise professionals. Prepare for next episodes about macOS AppKit, Linux kernel, Go microservices and Plan 9 vs. Inferno. And maybe gardening at some point. Also — April Fools!
Seriously though — the episode is a great introduction into C# world. Just for erudition sake, you know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 16: Tools</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/16-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/16-tools/</guid>
      <description>In this episode Artem, Artur and Hannes discuss the tools they use for development.
Tools:
 Mainframer Composer Swarmer zsh cloc ncdu tig ag  CI:
 Jenkins CircleCi Drone  Libraries:
 Spek RxReplayingShare Moshi  Hosts  Artem Zinnatullin: Twitter, GitHub, blog Artur Dryomov: Twitter, GitHub, blog Hannes Dorfmann: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 15: 2017 in Retrospective</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/15-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/15-2017/</guid>
      <description>In this episode Artur and Hannes do a retrospective on 2017. They share their personal highlights, favorite talks, disapointments, learnings and much more.
Links
Talks
 Two Stones, One Bird: Implementation Tradeoffs by Christina Lee - KotlinConf 2017 Testing Kotlin at Scale: Spek by Artem Zinnatullin - KotlinConf 2017 The Reactive Workflow Pattern (Droidcon New York 2017) and Update (Droidcon San Francisco) by Ray Ryan The Resurgence of SQL by Jake Wharton and Alec Strong - Droidcon New York City 2017 Embracing SQL Without Abstraction by Alec Strong - Droidcon New York City 2016 OpenYOLO: Authentication made easy and secure by Iain McGinniss - Droidcon London 2017 and corresponding blog post  Libraries</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 14: RxJava — the Present and Future with David Karnok (core maintainer)</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/14-rxjava/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/14-rxjava/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we chatted with core maintainer David Karnok about the present and the future of RxJava.
In this episode Artem and Hannes chatted with David Karnok about present and future of RxJava. We discussed:
 RxJava 3 Preview Kaushik Gopal&amp;rsquo;s blog post: RxJava 1 -&amp;gt; RxJava 2 (Understanding the Changes) Artem Zinnatullin&amp;rsquo;s Reply to Kaushik Gopal&amp;rsquo;s aricle: &amp;ldquo;RxJava 1 -&amp;gt; RxJava 2 (Understanding the Changes)&amp;rdquo; Kotlin Coroutines Reagent: Experiments for future reactive libraries by using Kotlin Coroutines by Jake Wharton RxJava vs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 13: Conductor with Eric Kuck</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/13-conductor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/13-conductor/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we talked about Conductor with creator Eric Kuck.
Announcement: We have a new Co-Host for our podcast: Welcome Artur Dryomov!
We think that we need at least two hosts on each episode to produce a high-quality content. Unfortunately, podcast production is time-consuming but now there are three hosts, so we can ensure that at least two of us have time to produce a new episode regularly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 12: Instant Apps with Lukas Olsen and Christian Bahl</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/12-instant-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/12-instant-apps/</guid>
      <description>Hannes chatted with his coworkes Lukas and Christian about Instant Apps.
We apologize for the bad sound quality and low sound volume.
Hannes chatted with his coworkes Lukas and Christian about Instant Apps. Unfortunately, Artem wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to join us for this episode. We have covered:
 How Instant Apps work Limitations Accelerated Mobile Pages (AMP) Gradle Plugins: com.android.instantapp and com.android.feature Sharing code between regular App and Instant App User Experience with Instant Apps Instant App Early Access Preview Program Our personal Google I/O 2017 highlights:  Life is Great and Everything Will Be Ok, Kotlin is Here Architecture Components Speeding Up Your Android Gradle Builds Introduction to Android Instant Apps   Links:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 11: Migration to RxJava 2 with Artur Dryomov from Juno</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/11-rxjava-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/11-rxjava-2/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve talked to Artur about Juno&amp;rsquo;s way to migrate their Android Riders App from RxJava 1 to RxJava 2.
We have covered:
 Migration strategy at Juno What&amp;rsquo;s different in RxJava 2.0? Null values in RxJava 2 Flowable or Observable? Other Rx Types: Single, Maybe and Completable RxJava 2 interop library RxJava 2: Default UncaughtExceptionHandler logs exceptions silently in jvm unit tests RxJava 3  Links:
 Juno&amp;rsquo;s Android Rider Team RxJava 2 Migration Specification RxKotlin RxJava 2 interop library What&amp;rsquo;s different in RxJava 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 10: Kotlin Language Design Nitpicking with Dmitry Jemerov from JetBrains</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/10-kotlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/10-kotlin/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve talked to Dmitry Jemerov from Kotlin team at JetBrains about some language design decisions made in Kotlin
We know about sound volume level issue #67 and tried our best to maximize it in this episode, but Artem used his crappy headphones mic instead of professional one and we couldn&amp;rsquo;t achieve what we wanted, sorry about that, we&amp;rsquo;ll try our best in next episode.
We&amp;rsquo;ve talked to Dmitry Jemerov aka @yole from Kotlin team at JetBrains about some language design decisions made in Kotlin:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 9, Part 2: Kotlin Gradle plugin, compilers and build systems with Alexey Tsvetkov</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/09.2-kotlin-gradle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/09.2-kotlin-gradle/</guid>
      <description>In the second part of episode 9 we have talked about build systems for android development: Gradle, Buck and Bazel
Important note for Pocket Casts app users: Thanks to the great support of Pocket Casts team we were able to fix the &amp;ldquo;download episodes issue&amp;rdquo; (see show nodes of episode 9, part 1).
We have continued our discussion with Alexey Tsvetkov. In the second part we have talked about build systems for android development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 9, Part 1: Kotlin Gradle plugin, compilers and build systems with Alexey Tsvetkov</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/09.1-kotlin-gradle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/09.1-kotlin-gradle/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we have talked to Alexey Tsvetkov from Jetbrains about Kotlin Gradle plugin, compilers and build systems.
Important note for Pocket Casts app users: Unfortunately Pocket Casts android app has a problem with downloading our episodes (to listen to them offline). It seems that while downloading their android app is using a old http client which doesn&amp;rsquo;t support latest TLS cipher standards we use on server side to host our episodes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 8: Damn Functional Programming with Paco Estevez</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/08-fp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/08-fp/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we have talked with Paco Estevez about Functional Programming and how he applies Functional Programming in his android apps.
In this episode we have talked with Paco Estevez about Functional Programming and how he applies Functional Programming in his android apps. We have covered:
 Concepts of Functional Programming Monads, Pure Functions, Immutability, Tuples, Union Types Pattern Matching Error Handling Functional Reactive Programming with RxJava Restoring state in Android apps  Links:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 7: React Native with Felipe Lima from Airbnb</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/07-react/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/07-react/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we have talked with Felipe Lima about React Native, a cross platform solution to build native mobile apps using JavaScript and React, and how React Native is used at Airbnb.
In this episode we have talked with Felipe Lima about React Native, a cross platform solution to build native mobile apps using JavaScript and React, and how React Native is used at Airbnb. We have covered:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 6, Part 2: Continuous Integration (CI) &amp;amp; Continuous Delivery (CD)</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/06.2-ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 07:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/06.2-ci/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we have talked about Continious Integration (CI) and Continuous Delivery (CD). Fernando Cejas gives us some insights how Soundcloud do CI and CD.
We have covered:
 UI Tests Continuous Integration Continuous Delivery Soundcloud&amp;rsquo;s CI &amp;amp; CD Pipeline Testing in general EVERYTHING &amp;amp; LIFE  Links:
 Slides from Fernando&amp;rsquo;s talk at MobileOptimized&amp;rsquo;2016  Fernando&amp;rsquo;s Clean Architecture sample on github From Prefab House to Lego House - Blog post about depending on a shared library  Guests  Fernando Cejas: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Hosts  Artem Zinnatullin: Twitter, GitHub, blog Hannes Dorfmann: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 6, Part 1: Continuous Integration (CI) &amp;amp; Continuous Delivery (CD)</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/06.1-ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/06.1-ci/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we have talked about Continious Integration (CI) and Continuous Delivery (CD). Fernando Cejas gives us some insights how Soundcloud do CI and CD.
We have covered:
 Continuous Integration Continuous Delivery Pair Programming Release Train Soundcloud&amp;rsquo;s CI &amp;amp; CD Pipeline Testing  Links:
 Slides from Fernando&amp;rsquo;s talk at MobileOptimized&amp;rsquo;2016  Fernando&amp;rsquo;s Clean Architecture sample on github  Guests  Fernando Cejas: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Hosts  Artem Zinnatullin: Twitter, GitHub, blog Hannes Dorfmann: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 5: Android TV </title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/05-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/05-tv/</guid>
      <description>In episode 5 we talked to Joe Birch about Android TV.
We have covered:
 What is Android TV Leanback Library MVP Pattern to share code between Phone and Android TV App Android TV Recommendation System What&amp;rsquo;s new in Android Nougat for Android TV  Links:
 Bourbon: Dribbble, Android, MVP and a Common-Code Module Vineyard: Creating an Android TV Vine App Android TV &amp;amp; Chill: A concept for what it would be like ordering fast-food on Android TV Code !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 4: Indie Development</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/04-indie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 05:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/04-indie/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we have talked about Indie Development.
We have covered:
 How to get started in Indie development Project management as single developer Testing and Continuous Integration How does an Indie developer decides which libraries or technologies to use? Designing without being a designer Play Store, in app purchases and subscriptions  Apps published by Chris Lacy on Google Play Store: - Action Launcher 3 - Action Launcher 2 - Tweet Lanes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 3, Part 2: RxJava with its core developer David Karnok</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/03.2-rxjava/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 20:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/03.2-rxjava/</guid>
      <description>In the second part of the episode we continued the discussion about RxJava.
More technical questions about RxJava. We have covered:
 Schedulers.computation() in RxJava Schedulers in RxJava subscribeOn() and observeOn() Testing code with RxJava Extending the Observable  Guests  David Karnok: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Hosts  Artem Zinnatullin: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 3, Part 1: RxJava with its core developer David Karnok</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/03.1-rxjava/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/03.1-rxjava/</guid>
      <description>In this part of the episode we have talked about RxJava.
We have covered:
 Past of RxJava Background of David Karnok and his earlier implementation of Reactive Extensions for JVM Current state of the RxJava development Reactive Streams specification JDK 9 Flow API RxJava v2 and Android compatibility  Guests  David Karnok: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Hosts  Artem Zinnatullin: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 2: Testing</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/02-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 06:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/02-testing/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we have talked about testing in Android Development.
In this episode we have talked about testing in Android Development. We have covered:
 Unit testing Integration testing Functional (UI) testing Robolectric Android Instrumentation API UI Automator Espresso Robotium Appium JUnit AssertJ Thruth Spock Spek Questions asked by listeners.  Open Source projects from Mike:
 Aftermath ColorArt  Links:
 #qualitymatters U2020 Android Needs A Simulator, Not An Emulator minSdkVersion for multiDex without flavors  Guests  Mike Evans: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Hosts  Artem Zinnatullin: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 1: Architecture of modern Android apps</title>
      <link>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/01-architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 20:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thecontext.github.com/website/episodes/01-architecture/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we have talked about software architecture on Android.
We covered:
 MVC MVVM MVVMC MVP Flux Cycle.js (a.k.a. Model-View-Intent)  Open Source projects from Hannes:
 Mosby SQLBrite-DAO FragmentArgs ParcelablePlease  Links:
 AutoValue split into 2 jars issue Dagger 2 document about testing Clean MVVM example Gradle&amp;rsquo;s incremental build issue with annotation processing  Guests  Hannes Dorfmann: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Hosts  Artem Zinnatullin: Twitter, GitHub, blog  Discussion Give us your opinion on the episode!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>